

HALİT UZAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

<u>halit.uzan@gmail.com</u> <u>+90 530 114 25 48</u>

halituzan.vercel.app

x.com/uzandev github.com/halituzan in linkedin.com/halituzan

EDUCATION

Karadeniz Teknik Üni.

Economy

2010-2014

SKILLS

- Typescript
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- ReactJs
- NextJs
- Tailwindcss
- Bootstrap
- Git
- NodeJs
- MongoDB(mongoose)

LANGUAGES

Ingilizce B1 seviye

HOBBIES

- Camping
- Trekking

ABOUT

After a 5-year e-commerce venture, I decided to focus on developing my skills in software development. While developing software for my e-commerce company, my interest in the field grew. I transitioned from amateur development to a professional career in software development by joining a bootcamp in 2020. Since then, I've left the e-commerce sector and have been developing software within the JavaScript ecosystem.

During this period, I've utilized JavaScript frameworks such as ReactJS and NextJS for my projects. I heavily relied on TailwindCSS and also used **Bootstrap** and **SCSS** technologies for styling. Additionally, I enriched my UI designs with libraries like MaterialUI, Mantine, and NextUI.

As my projects grew, I realized the challenges of state management and thus learned to use Redux and Redux Toolkit in my new projects. To overcome the difficulties of teamwork, I improved my skills in using **ESLint** and started learning **TypeScript** to work on type-controlled projects. While enhancing my skills in these areas, I also learned **NodeJS** and started using **MongoDB** to continue developing my projects as a Full-Stack developer.

WORK HISTORY

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (INTERN)

ETurnsoft, Turkey / Istanbul 2021-2024

I worked on administration panels and user management systems. Technologies used: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Bootstrap, and MongoDB.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Codelisa Teknoloji, Turkey / Istanbul 2022 - 2024

I have worked on customer-focused, modular websites and mobile applications.

Technologies used: Typescript, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Reacts, NextJs(SSR), TailwindCss and Micro-Frontend